

COMMERCIAL Professional

BORN: 07, JAN, 1987



ABOUT ME

My name is Mustafa Bassam, I'm currently looking for a job under commercial field. I have 10 years of experience working with many of companies and agencies. I have a bachelor's degree in languages and societies. I consider myself i have a good public experiance in life and business managment, motivated and professional individual with experience in the marketing and sales. proven leader of teams and projects.



CONTACT

Address:

Iraq, Kurdistan region

Mobile 1:

+ 964 782 445 6677

Mobile 2:

+ 964 750 749 8986

Email:

mustafa.bassam@hotmail.nl

Skype:

akrawy2000

LinkedIn:

Mustafa Akrawy

- ENGLISH
- Good
- KURDISH
- Good
- ARABIC
- FLUENT
- DUTCH
- Middle



SKILLS

SOCIAL NETWORKS COMMUNICATION **MANAGMENT**

STRATEGY BUILDING O

PI ANING





EXPERIENCES

COMMERCIAL MANAGER

2019 - 2020

FIBERBAND ISP - KURDISTAN REGION

- Making business growth strategies to help meet organizational goals and objectives,
- Build and nurture client relationships in order to continue winning new contracts.
- Working with other department heads to determine company goals and KPIs,
- Conduct market research to inform strategic business decisions,
- Oversee branding and marketing endeavors to ensure all efforts are aligned with business goals.
- Negotiate new projects and contract terms with new client.

MARKETING COMMUNICATION

PROFESSIONAL

2013 - 2018

FIFI D FORCE TEAM

2012 - 2013

BRANCH MANAGER

2012

MARKETING SEGMENTATION

SPECIALIST

2010 - 2011

EVENTS & SPONSORSHIP

SUPERVISOR

2009 - 2010

CALL CENTER REPRESENTATIVE

2006 - 2009

ZAIN IRAQ - KURDISTAN REGION

ZAIN IRAQ - KURDISTAN REGION

12 INTERNATIONAL COMPANY - KURDISTAN REGION

KPN, TELECOM - AMSTERDAM, NL

POST NL EXPRESS - AMSTERDAM, NL

MTC ATHEER - BAGHDAD, IRAQ



EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF AMSTERDAM

LANGUAGES AND SOCIETIES DEPT. / BSC

2011

AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS

HIGH SCHOOL

AL MANSOUR HIGH SCHOOL

BAGHDAD, IRAQ



2005

REFERENCE

TARZA RZGAR

Director HR AND ADMIN, FIBERBAND ISP

Phone: +964 751 741 1615 Email: tarza.rzgar@fiberband.net EYMAN TSSAI

Head of Marketing, ZAIN IRAQ Phone: +964 780 6999 736 Email: Eyman.Tssai@iq.zain.com